<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Decarb Direct Partners</title>
    <link>https://decarbdirect.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Decarb Direct Partners</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://decarbdirect.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GHG dashboard</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/products/dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/products/dashboard/</guid>
      <description>GHG dashboard A GHG dashboard is a digital tool that provides a quick overview of an organization&amp;rsquo;s greenhouse gas emissions. It offers real-time data visualization, emission breakdown by source, historical analysis, and goal tracking. Users can easily monitor emissions, identify trends, and track progress towards sustainability targets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHG Analytics</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/products/analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/products/analytics/</guid>
      <description>GHG Analytics GHG analytics function enables the analysis of greenhouse gas emissions data to identify trends, patterns, and insights. It helps organizations understand their carbon footprint, track emission sources, and evaluate the effectiveness of emission reduction strategies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GHG Reporting</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/products/reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/products/reporting/</guid>
      <description>GHG Reporting The GHG Reporting enables users to accurately measure, track, and report greenhouse gas emissions data. It simplifies the process of collecting emission data from various sources, ensuring compliance with regulatory requirements and facilitating transparent communication of environmental performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decarb Solutions</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/products/solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/products/solutions/</guid>
      <description>Decarb Solutions The Decarbonization Solutions showcases innovative strategies and technologies aimed at reducing carbon emissions and promoting sustainability. It provides users with insights into various decarbonization initiatives, including renewable energy adoption, energy efficiency improvements, carbon capture and storage, and sustainable transportation solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Báo cáo đánh giá thứ sáu IPCC</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/resources/ar6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/resources/ar6/</guid>
      <description>Báo cáo thứ sáu (AR6) của Ủy ban liên chính phủ về biến đổi khí hậu (IPCC) là báo cáo được biên soạn cho nhiệm kỳ 2015-2023 nhằm đánh giá thông tin khoa học, kỹ thuật và kinh tế xã hội liên quan đến biến đổi khí hậu.&#xA;Tóm tắt cho các nhà hoạch định chính sách&#xA;Báo cáo tổng hợp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hướng Dẫn Kiểm Kê Khí Nhà Kính Quốc Gia IPCC 2006 (cập nhật 2019)</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/resources/2006-ipcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/resources/2006-ipcc/</guid>
      <description>Hướng dẫn của IPCC năm 2006 về Kiểm kê Khí nhà kính Quốc gia cung cấp một khuôn khổ tiêu chuẩn hóa cho các quốc gia đo lường và báo cáo có hệ thống lượng phát thải và loại bỏ khí nhà kính trên nhiều lĩnh vực khác nhau.&#xA;Bản Điều chỉnh năm 2019 cập nhật những tiến bộ khoa học và kỹ thuật mới nhất, nâng cao các phương pháp, hệ số phát thải và hướng dẫn cho các vấn đề mới nổi, do đó cải thiện độ chính xác và độ tin cậy của các kiểm kê GHG quốc gia cần thiết cho việc giảm nhẹ và xây dựng chính sách biến đổi khí hậu hiệu quả.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoả thuận Paris: nền tảng chính sách khí hậu toàn cầu</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/resources/the-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/resources/the-paris/</guid>
      <description>Thỏa thuận Paris, được thông qua vào ngày 12 tháng 12 năm 2015, là một hiệp ước quốc tế quan trọng nhằm thích ứng biến đổi khí hậu và giảm thiểu tác động của biến đổi khí hậu. Hiệp ước này tập hợp 195 quốc gia với mục tiêu hướng tới kiềm chế sự gia tăng nhiệt độ toàn cầu xuống dưới 2 độ C so với mức tiền công nghiệp, đồng thời nỗ lực hành động để hạn chế sự gia tăng này ở mức 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ Các câu hỏi thường gặp</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Contact us today to learn more about how our decarbonization consulting services can benefit your organization.&#xA;1. What is greenhouse gas accounting, and why is it important for businesses? Greenhouse gas accounting involves measuring, reporting, and managing emissions of gases that contribute to climate change. It&amp;rsquo;s important for businesses to understand their emissions to mitigate climate impact, comply with regulations, and enhance sustainability.&#xA;2. How do you collect and analyze greenhouse gas emissions data?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hợp tác</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/partnership/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you we&amp;rsquo;re committed to driving positive change through decarbonization consulting. Our team of experts specializes in providing tailored solutions to help businesses and organizations reduce their carbon footprint and transition towards sustainable practices. From assessing current emissions to implementing strategic initiatives, we&amp;rsquo;re dedicated to guiding you towards a greener, more sustainable future.&#xA;Contact us today to learn more about how our decarbonization consulting services can benefit your organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liên hệ</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Chúng tôi luôn sẵn sàng hỗ trợ Decarb Direct cam kết đồng hành cùng quý công ty trên hành trình giảm phát thải khí nhà kính, hướng tới phát triển bền vững.&#xA;Để bắt đầu hành trình chuyển đổi xanh và bền vững, liên hệ ngay với Decarb Direct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sứ mệnh &amp; Tầm nhìn</title>
      <link>https://decarbdirect.com/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://decarbdirect.com/mission/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you we&amp;rsquo;re committed to driving positive change through decarbonization consulting. Our team of experts specializes in providing tailored solutions to help businesses and organizations reduce their carbon footprint and transition towards sustainable practices. From assessing current emissions to implementing strategic initiatives, we&amp;rsquo;re dedicated to guiding you towards a greener, more sustainable future.&#xA;Contact us today to learn more about how our decarbonization consulting services can benefit your organization.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
